[The Old Story of Yu Hong]
[Episode 24]
Qianqian, which episode is on?
Episode three.
What... is it about?
Wh-What is it about?
See for yourself.
See for myself, huh?
Juan.
Back in our day,
what did we watch?
Just cartoons like...
Havoc in Heaven,
the Avanti series,
and other stuff, right?
I can't hear the TV now.
You can't hear the TV.
Juan,
you practically
ordered an entire menu today.
What? Are you still hungry?
You're eating so many sunflower seeds.
If necessary...
m-maybe you should go to that diner again.
J-Just tell me
what you want to do with me.
How else should I be punished
to make you feel better?
Go to bed, Qianqian.
It's time.
I'll tell you a story.
What are you doing?
Didn't you tell me to kowtow
and apologize?
Move.
Good dogs never stand in the way.
Juan, Juan.
I'm just feeling edgy.
I've been here for days,
yet there hasn't been a result.
I thought I'd go back
after solving the case.
Or it'd be too embarrassing.
Are you that eager to leave?
I'm eager to solve the case.
But I don't think I'm wrong.
You should leave soon.
If not, even Qianqian will be
found suspicious.
She arrived the day Zhao Changyou died.
See, as I told you,
this kid's way too clever.
I should investigate her too.
Why not investigate me as well?
Where did Zhao Changyou lose his life?
In my jurisdiction.
Who was the witness?
It was me.
Such a coincidence, huh?
Where did Li Dewu die?
Also in my jurisdiction.
So who's the biggest suspect?
It's still me.
I did both killings.
You...
I...
My supervisor asked me to return
and report to him in a few days.
Before my departure,
can you go look for clues with me?
What do you want?
To eat.
Something just crossed my mind.
Today, when I was
driving and passing No. 2 Road,
a kid suddenly rushed out
from the side of the road.
Thank God I reacted fast
enough to slam on the brakes.
If I had hit the kid,
he would've been terribly injured, right?
Which kindergarten does your kid go to?
No. 2 Road Kindergarten.
What a coincidence.
When your child
crosses No. 2 Road in the future,
he had better be extra careful.
Getting hit by a car
is no small matter.
Do you hear me?
Yes, I hear you.
[Platform 1]
He Liang!
Liang.
[Platform 1]
Why...
Why did you leave without saying goodbye?
That's not very nice.
When will you be back?
When would you like me to be back?
I don't know.
You adults never keep your word.
Dad said he'd pick me up in three months.
I promise I'll come visit you.
It's a deal then.
Pinky swear. Once a word is given,
-it must be kept.
-It must be kept.
He'll be back.
Give me a smile now.
Juan went out on a call.
S-She's too busy to come here today.
So,
she had us bid you farewell in her stead.
♪ Cold and warm, when can they rest? ♪
Okay, you can go now.
♪ Looking back, how many autumns? ♪
How tall are you now?
You're growing taller and taller.
♪ Searched everywhere, yet lost instead ♪
Let's watch Ikkyu-san.
♪ What I didn't hope for is in my hand. ♪
You've grown taller, Qianqian.
♪ Did I get it or not? ♪
♪ Can't explain the gains and losses,
the mistakes ♪
♪ Just heard and saw, then it changed ♪
Shake it. Get your body moving.
Work your body.
Shake it.
♪ No idea where to trace it back ♪
We are little gorillas.
Take a look.
♪ What do I seek in my whole life? ♪
If you can't read it, just follow
the phonetic spelling.
♪ Always deciding
what to give up and what to hold ♪
Do you know any swear words
in Cantonese?
The ruder, the better.
Teach me a few.
♪ I've worn out this life of mine ♪
So I can curse her father out
when I see him again.
You have to be that mean?
♪ Yet what I reach for
has already run away ♪
Is that mean?
What he did isn't exactly human, is it?
♪ What do I seek in my whole life? ♪
♪ In confusion, I can never
see it through ♪
♪ I didn't expect what I lost ♪
♪ Was already all I had ♪
[Tiecheng Station]
He Liang.
♪ Cold and warm, when can they rest? ♪
You couldn't be more careless.
I can't believe you left behind
something so expensive.
♪ Looking back, how many autumns? ♪
♪ Searched everywhere, yet lost instead ♪
I thought
you wouldn't come see me off.
♪ What I didn't hope for is in my hand. ♪
You think I'm that petty?
♪ Did I get it or not? ♪
You left without saying goodbye.
♪ Can't explain the gains and losses,
the mistakes ♪
I hate it when people do that.
♪ Just heard and saw, then it changed ♪
You're just like Qianqian's father.
How is that any way to behave?
♪ No idea where to trace it back ♪
You keep the recorder for now.
♪ What do I seek in my whole life? ♪
Just give it back to me
when I return.
♪ Always deciding
what to give up and what to hold ♪
You will be back here?
♪ I've worn out this life of mine ♪
♪ Yet what I reach for
has already run away ♪
That can't be true.
You men
always make empty promises.
♪ What do I seek in my whole life? ♪
I haven't solved the case yet.
For the sake of that,
I'll have to come back here.
♪ In confusion, I can never
see it through ♪
Off you go.
It's been a pleasure
spending these days with you.
♪ I didn't expect what I lost ♪
♪ Was already all I had ♪
Just come back in five years.
D-Don't leave a drop
in your glasses, guys.
Quick.
Drink up.
Hey, Hong.
Come on.
Have one more drink with me.
I can't, Mr. Lu.
One last drink.
I've had one too many.
You drink with others.
Just finish this one last cup.
I propose
that they drink in wedding style.
Yes, in wedding style!
Do it now!
Drink in wedding style!
You drink with him. I won't.
-How am I supposed to do it alone?
-Mr. Lu.
Mr. Lu!
Mr. Lu.
Here's the thing.
Ms. Chen has an upset stomach today.
I'll drink this up for her.
Can someone else take one's place
in having a wedding-style drink?
Fine.
Let's play by the usual rules.
For each drink you have for her,
take two more.
He can really hold his liquor.
Then let's keep going.
Here, the submarine style.
Drink up!
Don't just stand there.
H-Hey, you.
Look...
L-Lad, I am
out of cigarettes.
Go buy me a new pack.
Off you go!
Liu,
Mr. Liang thinks
you're being a nuisance now.
With you standing in the way,
Ms. Chen won't get to finish
that wedding-style drink.
Right?
Waitress!
Hello.
Buy two packs of State Express 555.
You may keep the change. Thanks.
Care a lot about your employee, don't you?
Is he going to work overtime
tonight?
Like, practicing reverse parking?
Reverse parking...
It's not like that, Mr. Liang.
You must be joking.
I'm just a driver.
-Driver? No.
-I...
Let me formally introduce him to everyone.
This is Liu Yang,
a proper graduate
from the Railway Vocational College.
He used to drive for me,
and that was purely transitional.
Li's driver quit, didn't he?
I couldn't find anyone smart
to fill his position
within such a short time.
So I had to make Liu settle for less.
From now on,
Liu is transferred
to a management position.
He'll be in charge of all orders
from outside the province.
Contracts, too.
What a mess we've created here.
Yang, quick.
Come on, a toast to Mr. Liu.
-Guys.
-Here it goes.
Mr. Liu, let me raise a toast to you.
Come on.
Let's drink together.
-Mr. Liu, Mr. Liu.
-This is to you.
Mr. Liu, here.
A toast to you.
Mr. Liang.
You like smoking State Express 555, right?
Listen.
A friend of mine happens to be abroad.
Next time he comes back,
I'll have him bring some for you.
And I'll personally deliver them to you.
How about that?
It's very kind of you.
Thank you very much.
N-No hassle for me at all.
Actually, I think I've been smoking
too much
lately.
It's like I'm addicted to it.
I really should quit smoking.
I'd like to propose a toast.
Well, if there's anything
lacking in hospitality today,
I hope you will forgive us.
Not at all.
Mr. Liu.
That's not true.
Please bear with us, everyone.
A toast to Mr. Liu.
Let's raise a toast to Mr. Liu.
Mr. Liu, a toast to you.
Mr. Lu.
I'll drink this up, Mr. Lu.
Let's not crowd up here.
Go over there.
Must have a drink with the beauty.
The arm, the arm.
Come on.
Perfect time to practice reverse parking.
Not a chance.
What time do you think it is?
I need to go home now.
Can your wife promote you to manager?
Or can she give you a child?
With her poor health,
is she even able to get intimate with you?
We made a pact, didn't we?
Things are better kept separate.
You're leaving a soft, plump woman
for that skinny one at home.
For a while after Li Dewu died,
I had nightmares every day.
I dreamed that he chased and beat me
with that severed hand of his.
But since I started sleeping with you,
I've never dreamed about him again.
I think I know why you married that girl.
You believe that by making her your wife,
all those things you did before
can be wiped clean.
Stop spewing nonsense.
Nonsense?
Nobody knows you better than I do,
Liu Yang.
We're birds of a feather.
Do you really think you can
instantly become a Buddha
after laying down your knife?
Who knows
what severe retribution awaits us?